

Chacha Zhou(周伟) □

Crypto.com - Foris Technology (Shenzhen) Limited / Senior Software Engineer

7 Years Experience / College Degree / 29 Years Old

Profile

Execution Team Spirit Self-driven Adaptability English

Over 7 years front-end experience, and developed many projects during this time, including **React** and **Vue** web app, **Blockchain Web3** dapp, **React-Native** app, WeChat **mini-program**, **Flutter** hybrid app, and also have some **Nodejs** experience, and as a team leader of 10 members before.

Work Experience



Crypto.com - Foris Technology (Shenzhen) Limited. / Exchange Team

2022.05-2023-01

Senior Software Engineer



- 1. As a senior software engineer in a large front-end team, responsible for the crypto.com Exchange core features development, including security dashboard, affiliate dashboard, etc.
- 2. Integrate Yubikey web authn to Exchange security dashboard with backend developers, and add Yubikey bridges for Android and iOS platform, improve web and app security.
- 3. Integrate components to UI component library X-UI, and develop UI developer tools to facilitate development and debugging, add Jest unit jest to UI components and improve test coverage.
- 4. Responsible for CI/CD for our Exchange and Yubikey project, integrate Circle CI and Github actions to our Exchange Vue3 migration project.
- 5. Responsible for technology architecture of Vue3 migration project, bring monorepo best practise and develop playground developer tools for Exchange Vue3 migration project and improve page development efficiency.



2019.01-2022.04



1. As the leader of the large front-end technical team, responsible for the project management and R&D of the web, mobile HTML5, mini-program and Flutter App, responsible for the mobile cross-platform technology R&D and project management, engineering and automatic deployment, technology selection and technology challenge.

- 2. Team management, task arrangement and scheduling, follow up front-end project development progress, improve frontend workflow and product experience, participate in product requirements, interaction and design discussions, and formulate suitable solutions
- 3. Team building, regularly hold technical sharing within the team, create a cultural atmosphere of engineers, regular team technical training, improve team technical level and R&D ability.
- 4. Responsible for visual monitoring of front-end large-screen robots, video monitoring and remote control of robots, as well as architecture design and technology research and development of visual graphics editing tools, and develop visual applications using D3, fabricJS, ThreeJS, and other frameworks.
- 5. Responsible for the cross-platform technology architecture design of native iOS and Android apps and Flutter, combined with native technology and Flutter cross-platform technology hybrid development, to solve the problem of multiple-end reuse of a set of codes.



OlympusLabs / R&D department

2018.08-2019.01

Front-end Developer

React) (Typescript) (Web3.js) (Redux)

- 1. Responsible for Web3 dapp and DeFi SDK development, connect front-end with ethereum smart contract and imToken wallet.
- 2. Develop Olympus Portal project which is a DeFi derivatives management system, improve front-end user experience and performance.
- 3. Connect dapp with Metamask and build user wallet account and transactions data visualization.
- 4. Improve front-end workflow and web app experience, participate in product requirements, interaction and design discussions, and formulate suitable solutions.



Plum Flower International LLC / R&D department / Full-time Remote

2017.06-2019.01

Front-end Team Leader

React Flow Jest NextJS Javascript

- 1. Served as the technical leader of a 7-person front-end development team from all over the world, responsible for frontend project technology research and development.
- 2. Team management, task arrangement and scheduling, follow up front-end project development progress, improve technical documentation.
- 3. Responsible for front-end performance optimization, front-end architecture design and technology selection, front-end engineering and automatic deployment of large-scale US municipal projects.
- 4. Improve front-end workflow and product experience, participate in product requirements, interaction and design discussions, and formulate suitable solutions.



For Change LLC / R&D department

2016.08-2017.06

Front-end Developer

Vue)

(VueX) (Node.js) (Javascript)

- 1. As a core member of the technical team, responsible for the front-end development technology selection, technical architecture, the front-end page refactoring, and implementation of interactive logic and create some amazing animations, data processing of the front-end, and develop progressive front-end page.
- 2. Use Express Nodejs framework as the middle layer to develop the front-end data interface, use Vue front-end framework to develop the book management system SPA, use Vuex as the data state management tool, use Gulp and Webpack to package and compress project files, and front-end development CI/CD.
- 3. Responsible for the front-end development of millions of user-level products, formulate product release processes and code specifications, and design WeChat WebApp multi-page project architecture and workflow.



Ai Ying Internet Culture Co., Ltd. / R&D department

2015.07-2016.08

Front-end Developer



React Jquery HTML5 Node.js

Responsible for the front-end development technology selection architecture design, the front-end page refactoring, and implementation of interactive logic. Use React + Redux + Ant Design + NodeJS + Webpack to build video editor O2O platform.

Project Experience

Crypto.com Exchange 2022.05-2023.01

Crypto.com Exchange is a large cryptocurrency exchange which is developed with Vue2 and Vue3 frameworks, and with over 70 million users worldwide.

- 1. Develop front-end features with Vue2 and Vue3 frameworks, develop UI components and add Jest unit tests, fix browser compatibility issues.
- 2. Integrate Circle CI and Github Actions to CI/CD workflow, integrate Javascript error monitoring tool to front-end system.
- 3. Responsible for Vue3 migration architecture design, explore multi-page and single-page application engineering development, and improve project maintainability and scalability.
- 4. Apply and config AWS infrastructure resources, optimize project deployment workflow, and improve deployment efficiency.

Sender Wallet 2022.07-Currently

Sender is a browser extension wallet built for near protocol, with the goal of providing a secure and easy-to-use wallet for DeFi and NFT users.

- 1. Build the basic technical architecture, and introduce **React**, **Redux** and **Webpack** to extension development.
- 2. Use ethers.js and near api to build cross multi-chain features, and develop Staking, Swap and NFT features.
- 3. Connect Ledger and Keystone hardware wallet to Sender wallet and improve account security.
- 4. Responsible for handling cross-browser compatibility issues.

The business management platform is a large-scale background management system for the robot industry, which integrates express delivery business, takeaway delivery business, and robot shared delivery business. It also includes device management and control platform, robot real-time monitoring system. Monitoring center, reconciliation management, user management, authority management, message center and other core business modules.

- 1. Use **React** and **Typescript** stack to build the basic technical architecture of the background management system from scratch, create front-end development, UI component library, **Jest** unit testing and **Git Workflow** specifications.
- 2. Responsible for the technology research and development of related core modules of the business management platform, including large-screen data monitoring, real-time robot monitoring based on **Websocket**, and use **D3** and **e-chart** to build robot data visualization.

Aurora Company App

Aurora Company App is an enterprise recruitment service SaaS application that integrates job posting, personnel recruitment and instant communication. Enterprises can publish recruitment information on this platform and communicate with candidates online. There is an Aurora Candidate App on the client side. Ordinary users can find suitable job opportunities on this platform, and at the same time, they can communicate with enterprises online, voice and video, and share files online.

- 1. As the front-end development leader, lead 6 developers from all over the world to develop collaboratively remotely, formulate detailed development tasks, reasonably assign tasks to team members, and ensure efficient team collaboration.
- 2. Design the front-end infrastructure and front-end development workflow, formulate a unified front-end modular development standard, and provide a stable architectural foundation for the team to write high-quality code.
- 3. Unify front-end code specifications, write front-end code specification documents, standardize front-end code styles, and establish code style Check Lists, provide team members with a good coding foundation.
- 4. Formulated the Git standardized workflow and front-end code review process, and worked with Devops developers to formulate the automatic deployment process of web applications to ensure the continuous integration and continuous delivery.
- 5. Formulate the development specifications and standards of the front-end UI component library, use Storybook to collaboratively develop common component libraries and component description documents, use Rollup to package and compress and publish the UI component library on NPM, providing for the development of web applications the possibility of multiplexing and expansion solves the coupling problem between multiple applications.
- 6. Formulate the front-end component Jest test specification, and worked with team members to write component test cases, which improved the front-end component test coverage and reduced the code error rate.

Eco Web App 2017.06-2018.09

EcoAppPro is the new standard for urban utility management software and is an efficient and modern mobile GIS integration system. The project is a responsive large-scale integrated front-end project developed using the react technology stack, including Communications, User Center, Assets, System Manager, Personnel, and Logbook.

1. As the head of front-end technology, design and build the front-end technology infrastructure, lead 5 front-end members to develop collaboratively, and formulate reasonable development tasks.

- 2. Write relatively common front-end development standards, assign tasks to team members on Jira, review member codes, and control the progress of front-end development to achieve agile project development.
- 3. The technology stacks used in the project include React, Redux, React-router, Recompose, Redux-saga, Flow and Semantic-ui-react, etc., and use the above technology stacks to build a stable and efficient front-end technology architecture, design and develop reusable front-end foundations components.
- 4. Develop fetch-based HTTP asynchronous request service, load server-side data asynchronously, process and cache complex data, and solve CORS cross-domain requests.
- 5. Use webpack to achieve a series of engineering development, including compression and packaging of front-end resource files, generation and merging of front-end CSS style files, front-end JS code segmentation and asynchronous loading, and use CDN caching services to improve the performance and experience of the web app.
- 6. Use Jest testing tool to build a front-end testing environment and write complete unit test cases for React components to improve components quality and test coverage.

Education

Shenzhen University 2021-Currently

Bachelor Degree / Computer Science and Applications

Shenzhen Polytechnic 2013-2016

College Degree / Communication Technology

English CET-6 / Fluent

Social



http://github.com/chachaxw